我知道你在烦恼什么
I know what's bothering you.
有人在你面前吃培根
Someone is eating bacon in front of you,
却一丢丢都不分给你吃
and not offering you any.
不是  斯坦  我不烦恼这个
No, Stan, that's not it.
那你是在烦恼你接受暗示的能力
Then are you, perhaps, bothered by your inability
太差了吗
to take a hint?
明天是新学期第一天  暑假放完了
Tomorrow's the first day of school. Summer's over.
我再也不能学弹吉他
No more learning how to play guitar or,
或者种树  或者在社区中心做志愿者了
planting trees, or volunteering at the community center.
你压根没做过这些事
You didn't do any of those things.
现在是永远做不了了
And now I never will.
给你  斯坦  想到上学我就饱了
Here, Stan. School's made me not hungry.
耶
Yeah!
感谢上学  不让一块培根吃剩
Thanks, school! No bacon left behind.
你知道那是火鸡熏肉的对吧
You do realize that it's turkey bacon?
又怎样  我吃过一只老鼠  我吐了
So, I've eaten a mouse, thrown it up,
我又把吐出来的吃回去了
and eaten it again.
我可不是那种娇生惯养的狗
I'm not what you would call fancy.
嘿  泰勒  你准备好了吗
Hey, Tyler. You ready to do it?
干嘛
Do what?
去年  我们商量过你全部科目要考到A和B
Last year, we agreed you could only keep your hair
你才能留这又傻又长的发型
this ridiculously long if you got all A's and B's.
但  你拿了不少C啊  孩子
Well, you got a couple of C's, buddy.
C就得剪  是时候剪你的头发了
And C is for cut. Time to cut your hair.
我还拿了个D  啊  我说这个干嘛
I also got a D... oh, why did I say that?
这是我们协商好的  泰勒
We had a deal, Tyler.
如果我们连这都不遵守
What kind of parents would we be
我们还算什么好父母呢
if we didn't follow through?
你们儿子都拿C和D了
Your son is getting C's and D's,
你们还能当得再差点吗
could you do any worse?
别这样  泰勒  我从你小时候就开始剪你的头发了
Come on, Tyler. I've been cutting your hair since
你以前可喜欢了
you were little and you've always liked it.
你觉得怎么剪  亲爱的  不如在这儿剪一刀
What do you think, hun? Maybe take this off here.
- 没错  再剪一下这里  - 对了  我可以削薄这里
- Yeah, and feather this here. - Oh, I could taper it here.
我觉得我的手卡在这了
I think my hand's stuck under here.
没关系  我等下全剪掉
Oh, I'm going to cut that all off.
行了  你已经把话说明白了
Okay, you made your point.
我今年一定会更努力学习的
I'm definitely going to study harder this year.
你们不用再装作要剪我头发了
No need to keep pretending you're really going to do this.
你们真的要剪我头发啊
You're really going to do this?
泰勒  我的剪刀还没下去呢
Tyler, I haven't even done anything yet.
看起来好好玩  我也试试
That looks like fun. Let me try.
我就知道你会惨叫的
I thought that might happen.
克洛伊  我们不能把自己的快乐建立在别人的痛苦之上
Chloe, we're not doing this for our entertainment.
我错过了吗  我要做点爆米花吗  你做爆米花没
Did I miss it? Should I make popcorn? Did you make popcorn?
为什么没人做爆米花啊
Why has no one made popcorn?
艾芙莉  就像我刚刚对妹妹说的一样
Avery, as I just got done telling your sister,
我们不能把自己的快乐建立在别人的痛苦之上
we're not doing this for your entertainment.
坐到我旁边来  这角度特好
Sit here next to me... it's the best view.
来点爆米花
Have some popcorn.
好了  泰勒  开剪了
Okay, Tyler, here we go.
我永远不会忘记你的
I'll never forget you.
噢  曼妙的身姿  如此多浪卷儿
Oh, so much body, so much wave.
噢  我最牵挂你了  乱卷卷
Oh, and I'll miss you most of all, frizzy cowlick.
嗯  起码这次我不是被剪的那个
Well, at least this time I wasn't the one being groomed.
啊  我这些年来也有过不少雷人的发型啊
And, man, I've had some pretty crazy haircuts over the years.
蜈蚣头
Cornrows.
束发
Pompadour.
蕾娅公主头
Princess Leia.
那么  你们觉得怎么样呢
So, what does everybody think?
呃  你确实能看到
Well, you can see his face which is...
他的脸
A fact.
看看我  我是头发天使
Look at me. I'm making Hair Angels.
我觉得还不错  泰勒
I think it looks great, Tyler.
你自己看着看着就习惯了
You're just going to have to get used to it.
把镜子给我
Hand me the mirror.
不
No!
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
时间轴： shortcut
翻译： Nodlehs
■
校订： WaitinZ
后期： WaitinZ  liloelva
狗狗博客  第二季第一集
Dog With a Blog  S02E01  Too Short
不
No!
噢  托尔斯泰
Oh, Tolstoy.
咦  你开起来很开心嘛  艾芙莉
Well, you seem happy, Avery.
- 你怎么知道的  - 嗯  主要是这个
- What gave me away? - Well, mainly this.
我好激动啊  斯坦
I'm just so excited, Stan,
因为今天是新学期第一天
because today's the first day of school.
我好爱上学  里面充满着读书和学习
I love school. All the reading and studying;
还有纠正老师时得到的那种快感
The rush you get when you correct a teacher.
就像骗一个骗子一样
It's like grifting a grifter.
我为什么要用摇滚兔子午餐盒
And why did I pick a Rock Star Rabbit lunchbox?
同学们肯定会叫我摇滚兔子的
Everyone's going to call me Rock Star Rabbit.
克洛伊  不会有人因为你的午餐盒而叫你摇滚兔子的
Chloe, no one's going to call you that because of your lunchbox.
噢  娘你不懂
Oh, Mommy.
去年我用了个小红午餐盒
Last year I picked a little red
同学们喊了我一年的小红帽
lunchbox and everyone called me little red all year.
我觉得原因不在这儿
I'm not sure that's why.
难不成是我头发的原因吗
What else could it be?
你不可能一辈子藏着你的头发的
You're not going to be able to hide it forever.
起码也得试试  对吧
Well I have to try, don't I?
真谢谢你  现在我要兑现承诺了
Thanks to you, now I have to follow through on something.
熊孩子们  第一天上学  别迟到了
All right. First day of school. Don't wanna be late.
泰勒  确保克洛伊安全到她教室
Tyler, make sure Chloe gets safely to her class.
艾芙莉  确保泰勒安全到他教室
Avery, make sure Tyler gets safely to his class.
琳赛
Lindsay!
慢着  我们现在都上初二了
Wait, we're in eighth grade now.
我们应该要酷一点
We should probably be a little more cool.
噢  你说的对  重来
Oh, you're right. Redo.
- 哟  - 嘿  你们好
- S'up. - Hey, guys.
麦克斯
Max!
很欣慰我们的小团体回归了
I'm so glad our little group is back.
哇  你居然说好话  你通常都很消极的
Wow, that's so nice. Usually you're so negative.
你们都在这儿我就安心了
I'm just relieved you're here.
我一直坚信这个暑假
I was certain that over the
我们其中一个会掉进一片流沙里
summer one of us would get sucked into a pit of quicksand.
这才是麦克斯嘛  但我们是不会掉进流沙里的
There's our Max. We're not getting sucked in quicksand.
人们都说不会的  到了出事的时候就晚了
That's what people always say, until the day it happens.
记住  越挣扎就沉得越快
And remember, struggling only makes it worse.
不过  最重要的是
Well, the important thing is,
我们都返校了  什么都没变
we're all back and nothing has changed.
不过  安妮有变化  她摘掉了牙套还
Okay, Annie has changed. She lost her braces and got her...
对啊
Yeah.
哇  娜塔莉好像高了一英尺  金也高了
Wow, Natalie's, like, a foot taller. And so is Kim.
布莱恩也高了  阿曼达也高了
And Brian. And Amanda.
还有佩奇  本  瑞切尔  兴晓・鲁宾斯坦  都高了
And Paige and Ben and Rachel and Xing Xao Rubenstein.
我是唯一一个没长高的
I'm the only one who didn't grow.
我感觉自己缩水了
I feel like I shrunk.
和同龄的孩子比的话
Well, only in comparison to all the other kids
你是挺矮的
who look their age.
噢  对不起  我好像帮倒忙了
Oh, sorry, I guess that's not helping.
我感觉每个人看着我在想
I feel like everyone's looking at me wondering...
看看艾芙莉  她为什么没长高
"Look at Avery! Why didn't she grow?"
我也不知道
I don't know why!
艾芙莉  你像疯子一样乱吼之前
Avery, no one was looking
根本没人在看你
at you until you shouted like a total loon.
大家都喜欢看疯子  这提醒了我
People look at total loons. Which reminds me,
我在超市看到你妈了
I saw your Mom at the supermarket.
艾芙莉  每个人长高的速度都不同  没什么大不了的
Avery, kids grow at different rates. It's not a big deal.
就是  我和你差不多高
Yeah, I'm about your height.
去年  你才到我温莎结这么高
Last year, you were up to my windsor knot.
- 你在长高  - 我知道  感觉身躯好庞大
- You're growing.   - I know. I feel huge.
长身体不完全像你想象中那么好
Growing's not all it's cracked up to be.
我这个暑假头大了一圈
I went up a hat size over the summer.
很多好看的软呢帽都戴不下了
Lost a lot of good fedoras.
所以  你就知足常乐吧你
So, count your blessings!
噢  我想孩子们了
Oh, I miss the kids.
真不敢相信他们要离开家一天
I can't believe they're going to be gone all day.
我真希望找到不想他们的办法
I wish there were some way I could miss them less.
嘿  我想到了
Hey! I've got it.
嗨  小艾芙莉  嗨  小泰勒  嗨  小克洛伊
Hi, little Avery. Hi, little Tyler. Hi, little Chloe.
你们会陪我的  对吧
You'll keep me company, won't you?
我为什么要用芝士来做啊
Why did I make them out of cheese?
不要  别弄了好吗  离我远点  丹尼
No, cut it out, okay? Leave me alone, Danny!
别这样  给我看看嘛
Come on! Let's see it.
能有多难看呢  一定很好笑
How bad can it be? I bet it's hilarious.
不行  头发太短了  我丑得跟怪兽似的
No! It's too short. It's hideous. I'm a monster.
你知道吗  我很尊重这一点
You know what? I respect that.
如果你不想给我看
If you don't want to show me,
我也不会逼你去
I'm not gonna pressure you to...
哈
Ha!
你太易猜透了
You are so predictable.
你说的对  我也不知道我
You're right, I don't know what I was...
哈
Ha!
兄弟  你做一件事之前  我就知道你要做了
Dude, I always know what you're going to do before you do it.
- 是啊  我也这么想的  - 够了  我只穿了三件连帽衫
- Yeah, I guess so. Ha! - Okay, I only wore three hoods.
我真的没预计到你还要扒
I had no idea you were gonna do that.
我待会儿找你们
I'll catch you guys later.
斯坦  我在上学呢
Stan, it's the middle of school.
你来这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
没错  我不应该在这
Good point, shouldn't be here.
不过  我来都来了  我们做什么好呢
So, as long as I'm here, what do you want to do?
你想一起出去吗  聊聊金妮和乔的八卦
You wanna hang? Maybe talk trash about Ginny and Joe?
她看上他什么了
What does she see in him?
我们学校没有一对叫金妮和乔的情侣
There's no couple at the school named Ginny and Joe.
那么  你是说金妮现在单身吗
So, what you're saying is Ginny is available?
你在这里干什么
What are you doing?
你是因为太想我们才过来的吗
Are you just here because you miss us?
啥  也不全是
What? Not "Just."
我一直想在绘画课上当一回活模特
I also was hoping to be a live model for the art class.
回家吧  我们放学了就回去
Go home, we'll be back after school.
好吧  不过他们会错过我的招牌“谁  我啊”姿势
Fine, but they'll be missing out on my "Who, me?" Pose...
谁  我啊
"Who, me?"
哇  那个新来的男孩是谁
Whoa, who's the new kid?
韦斯・曼宁  在网上查过他底细了
Wes Manning. Looked him up on the Internet.
他今年六十四岁
He's a 64-year-old
是个从新泽西州特纳夫莱来的退休机械师
retired machinist from Tenafly, New Jersey.
感谢互联网
Thank you, Internet.
他好帅啊  你们留在这里  我去装路过
He's really cute. Wait here, I'm gonna do a walk-by.
你们可能觉得我的想法很奇怪
You'll probably think I'm weird,
不过我挺激动的
but I'm kind of excited.
我很喜欢上学
I really like school.
喜欢上学
Likes school!
我喜欢聪明有趣的女孩
I like girls who are smart and funny.
喜欢聪明有趣的女孩
Likes smart, funny girls.
因为我们在读《动物农庄》
So, because we were reading Animal Farm,
（注：乔治・奥威尔政治讽喻小说）
他就带我们去一个动物园玩
he took us on a field trip to a petting zoo.
你让一个橄榄球教练
That's what happens when you
来上英语课  就会闹出这种笑话
let a football Coach teach an English class.
小伙伴们  他喜欢阅读和嘲笑橄榄球教练
Guys, he likes reading and making fun of football coaches.
他真完美
He's perfect!
- 那么  你应该去和他说话  - 不要  我不行的
- Well, you should go talk to him. - No. I can't.
我是说  他可能只喜欢
I mean, he probably only
暑假里长高了的女孩
likes the tall girls who grew over the summer.
噢  别傻了  你聪明有趣  长得还漂亮
Oh, that's crazy. You're smart and funny and really cute.
和他说话吧  最糟能糟到哪里去呢
Just talk to him. What's the worst that could happen?
你走到那里  然后被绊倒  又吐在了自己身上
You walk over there, you trip, you throw up on yourself.
这叫绊吐
It's called the trip-puke.
好  我就这么办吧
Okay. I'm gonna do it.
我的意思是  照琳赛说的做  不是去绊吐
I mean, what Lindsay said, not the trip-puke.
没人会故意绊吐的  它该发生时就发生
Nobody plans the trip-puke. It just happens.
看看那些六年级的小学生
Just look at the sixth graders.
还记得我们这么小的时候吗
Remember when we were that little?
好了  我没有  我不是  我才不是
Okay, I don't... I'm not... I don't even...
我只是  我只是
I'm just... I'm just...
太矮了
Too short.
太矮了  太矮了  太矮了
Too short! Too short! Too short!
我知道太短了  别再笑我了
I know it is! Stop mocking me!
你回来了  你回来了
You're home, you're home!
噢  我都不记得你离家多少个春秋了
Oh, I don't know if you've been gone months or years,
我更不确定你到底回不回来了
but I wasn't sure if you were ever coming back!
斯坦  我只是早上才出家门去上第一天学
Stan, I just left this morning for the first day of school.
但你连一张明信片都没寄过来
And you didn't send one postcard.
啊  你回家啦  你回家啦
Oh, you're home! You're home!
噢  我知道只过了一天  但我想死你了
Oh, I know it's only been a day, but I've missed you so much!
唉  感觉像过了一年
Ugh, it felt like a year.
说到我心坎里去了
That's what I was saying!
你知道应该要上下移动的吧
You know you're supposed to go up and down.
我是想长高点  不是想长壮点
I'm trying to get taller, not stronger.
你这样只会拉长你的手
You'll just make your arms longer.
等你的手长得耷拉在地上时  你就会像只小猩猩
They'll drag on the ground and you'll look like a chimp.
别光考虑你自己了
Now stop being so self-involved
快帮我想想我的头发怎么办
and help me figure out what to do about my hair!
你可以不要再纠结你的发型了吗
Will you stop obsessing over your stupid hair?!
- 我头发太短了  - 我整个身子都太短了
- My hair is too short! - My whole body is too short!
没错  所以基本上没人会看到你
Exactly, so you're practically invisible.
你的问题不是问题
Your problem doesn't matter.
我这么高  别人能看到我
I'm up here, where people can see.
艾芙莉怎么了
What's wrong with Avery?
她在烦恼她的身体
She's upset about her body.
好了  艾伦  你已经准备好面对这个时刻的到来
Okay, Ellen, you've been preparing for this moment.
你不会像你妈一样搞砸的
You're not gonna mess it up like your Mom did.
我必须先和自己来个小谈话
I had to have my little talk with myself.
我现在已经在谈了  聊得很愉快  艾伦
Which I'm doing right now. Good talk, Ellen.
小甜心
Sweetie...
我明白你有些身体上的困扰
I understand you are having issues with your body.
所以  我们来说点女生的悄悄话吧
So, let's have a little gal chat.
你只要告诉我你的问题和疑虑
You tell me what your questions or concerns are.
我就会用这么多年来
I'll offer you the wisdom I've
积累的女性经验来帮你解决
collected from my experiences as a lifelong woman.
现在  你说出身体的一个部位  我们来聊聊
Now, just point to a part of your body and we'll talk about it.
我和自己谈这事的时候
That talk went so much better
效果比现在好多了
when I gave it to myself.
克洛伊  二年级的第一天怎么样
Chloe, how was the first day of second grade?
我学到了“大象”这词里面有个P
I learned that "Elephant" Has a P in it.
我不明白你们为什么没有告诉我
I don't know why no one here told me that.
午餐盒受欢迎吗
How'd the lunchbox go over?
午餐盒已经不重要了
The lunchbox didn't matter.
在二年级  里面的东西才重要
In second grade, what matters is what's inside.
我告诉克洛伊这样真的挺好的
I told Chloe that's actually kind of nice.
就像一个人  外在的东西并不重要
Like with a person. What matters isn't what's on the...
在车上你没让我心情变好
Didn't make me feel better in the car.
现在你也没让我心情变好
Not making me feel better now.
我以为我给你做了一顿很丰盛的午餐呢
I thought I made you a very nice lunch.
很明显  亲爱的  午餐时间要交换食物
Well, apparently, hon, lunchtime is all about trading.
你做的午餐没有交换的价值
Your lunch had no trade value.
- 我只换到了这个  - 一只香蕉
- This was all I could get for it. - A banana?
不是  只有蕉皮
No. Just the peel.
但他们没有换走你的午餐
But they didn't take your lunch.
这是块表示可怜的蕉皮
It was a pity peel.
我之前不知道午餐有这么重要
I didn't realize it was such a big deal.
我明天一定会用心做一顿丰盛的午餐给你的
I'll try and make you a really great lunch for tomorrow.
谢谢妈妈  我知道你会说到做到的
Thanks, Mommy! I knew you'd come through.
我相信你
I believe in you!
噢  你真贴心啊小乖乖  你的鼓励对我意义重大
Aw, that's so sweet, honey. It means so much to me.
你是对的  爸爸  她喜欢听鼓励的话
You're right, Daddy, she responds to encouragement.
当然  我在车上教你的东西也不是一无是处啊
Well, not everything I taught you in the car was useless.
好了  我一直在思考我的身高问题
All right, I've been thinking about my problem, and I'm
我要行动起来  妈  你开车带我去商场
going to take action Mom, you're driving me to the Mall.
噢  太好了  小甜心  在去的路上
Oh, that's great sweetheart on the way there...
如果你敢和我说女生悄悄话
If you try to gal talk me on the drive...
我就在高速公路上跳出你的车
I will stunt roll out of the moving car onto the freeway.
呃  不是在车子开着的时候跳  我又不傻
Well, not out of the moving car. I'm not a stunt woman.
我的意思是  我会在完全没有危险的时候离开你的车
The point is, I'm out of there as soon as it's completely safe.
艾芙莉说她逛了商场之后就解决了她的问题
Avery said she went to the Mall and fixed her problem.
我想知道她做了什么
I wonder what she did.
我觉得是这个
I think that.
好看吗  这双高跟鞋增高了六英寸
So, these platforms add six inches...
头发增高了八英寸
The hair's another eight, and
衣服上的竖纹产生的错觉又增高了两英寸
the vertical stripes add the illusion of two more.
你们觉得怎么样
What do you think?
我们该怎么处理
How are we playing this?
是说她需要听的还是她想听的
What she needs to hear or what she wants to hear?
艾芙莉  你看起来很不错
Avery, you look great!
说她想听的  懂了
Wants to hear... got it.
你看起来很高
You look tall.
是啊  我要在我自信心摧毁之前去和韦斯说话
Well, I better go talk to Wes before I lose my confidence.
如果你不能书写自己的命运
What's the point of looking like
又何必装成一支铅笔呢
a giant pencil if you can't write your own destiny?
- 嗨  我叫艾芙莉  - 对不起  没空
- Hi, I'm Avery. - Sorry, not now.
斯坦  过来
Stan, come here!
我以为我说清楚了  你不准来学校看我们
I thought I told you, you can't come to see us at school.
我真的好担心
I was just so worried about
金妮和乔能不能熬过分手的伤痛
how Ginny and Joe were taking the break-up.
- 金妮和乔复合了  - 他们复合了
- Ginny and Joe are made up. - They made up?
太棒了
That's great.
那两个傻孩子的确值得拥有一个重新开始的机会
Those two crazy kids deserve a chance.
斯坦  你要学会接受
Stan, you've gotta accept
我们现在每天都得上学这个事实
that we're going to school every day now.
你不能经常没事就跑过来
You can't be hanging around here so much.
你怎么会觉得我经常没事就跑过来呢
What makes you think I'm hanging around so much?
雕像虽然没穿衣服  但它们味道真不错
They're nudes, but they're tasteful.
艾芙莉吗  这张被子下面盖的是你吗
Avery? Is that lump under the covers you?
你觉得呢  斯坦
What do you think, Stan?
尺寸和形状都和你很相似
Well, the lump is about your size and shape.
声音听起来挺像你  闻起来也像
And has your voice, and smells like you.
所以不是你就是只鸭子
So, it's either you or a duck.
我以后都不想再上学了
I don't ever want to go back to school again.
但是艾芙莉很喜欢上学
But Avery loves school.
你对艾芙莉做了些什么  臭鸭子
What did you do with Avery, duck?
我是全年级最矮的  斯坦
I'm the smallest kid in my grade, Stan.
我不合群了
I just don't fit in.
艾芙莉  你的身高和你的自身价值没有关系
Avery, your size has nothing to do with your worth.
我是不是比那些蹲在女人手袋里
Am I worth more than one of
的小狗狗更有价值呢
those little dogs that women carry in their purses?
当然是了
Yes, I am.
举错例子了
That's a bad example.
我就是那种小狗狗  斯坦
I am the purse dog, Stan.
那个叫韦斯的男孩不肯跟我说话
I mean, this boy Wes won't even talk to me.
因为你的身高吗
Because of your height?
他喊我“六年级小学生”
He called me a "Little sixth grader"
而且今天他完全无视我
and then today he totally blew me off.
如果不是因为我矮  他为什么要这样对我
Why would he do that if it wasn't because I'm short?
太悲催了  不过你现在有个选择
That's terrible. But now you have a choice.
蹲手袋小狗狗也分两种  发抖型和凶猛型
There are two kinds of purse dogs; Shivering or vicious.
你是哪一种  艾芙莉
Which one are you, Avery?
我有点神经紧张
I am a little high-strung.
还有点爱冷酷待人
I have a tendency to get cold.
- 我少食多餐  - 你是凶猛型
- I eat small, but frequent, meals. - Say "Vicious."
- 凶猛型  - 没错  你就是
- Vicious! - Yeah, you are.
对耶  我很凶猛  并且我还要骂他一顿
Yeah, I am. And I'm gonna give him a piece of my mind.
明天  我要在学校里告诉他  他有多混蛋
Tomorrow at school, I'm going to tell him what a jerk he is.
他才是应该对自己的行为感到羞愧的人  而不是我
He's the one who should feel bad about this, not me.
这才是你嘛  或者是手袋小狗狗  或者是鸭子
Thatagirl! Or purse dog. Or duck.
随便你是什么
Or whatever you are.
嘿  艾芙莉  你妈妈告诉我
Hey, Avery. Your Mother tells
你对自己的身体有些困扰
me you've been having some issues with your body.
咳  我知道她的方法有点烦人
Well... I know her approach may have been a little off-putting.
但你走运了  因为我有小河马哈蕾
But lucky for you, I have Harriet the hippo.
哈蕾也对她现在的身体变化
Now, Harriet's has her insecurities
感到很害怕
about her changing body, too.
我想知道她们怎么
I wonder what they...
哈蕾  你吓着人了
Harriet, you scare people.
妈妈  亏我相信过你
Mommy, I believed in you.
这对我意义重大
And that means a lot to me.
相  信  过
Believed.
别告诉我今天的午餐又不行
Don't tell me today's lunch was no good, either.
我用昨晚剩的鸡肉给你做了个很好吃的三明治
I made you a very nice sandwich with leftover chicken.
你叫我怎么交换食物
How can I trade this?
你看看它拿起来长什么样
Look what happens when you pick it up.
所以小朋友都管它叫“掉馅灾难烂三明治”
All the kids called it the "Fall apart disaster stink sandwich."
听起来真傻
That's not even clever.
你还想咋地  我们才二年级
What do you want? We're in second grade.
我不明白这怎么又成问题了
I don't understand why this is a problem now.
你在一年级是没有这个问题啊
This wasn't a problem in first grade.
一年级的时候  我们浆糊泥土什么的都吃
In first grade, we'd eat anything. Paste, mud...
托尼吃过他的鞋带
Tony ate his shoelaces.
因为这事儿学校还开过大会呢
We had to have an assembly about it.
但是我们现在都二年级了
But now we're in second grade...
除了托尼留级
Except for Tony.
我们想吃点正常的
We want something good.
我要带一些能交换的食物
I need something I can trade.
艾芙莉二年级时的午餐是怎样的
What did Avery do in second grade?
她自己做的
She made her own lunch.
哦  反正我是不会自己做的
Yeah, I am not gonna do that.
好吧  那你明天午餐想要什么
Fine, so what do you want in your lunch tomorrow?
- 要十块钱  - 哦  反正我是不会给的
- Ten dollars. - Yeah, I am not gonna do that.
嘿  艾芙莉  我想过你的问题了
Oh, hey, Avery. I've been thinking about your problem,
你要不要考虑一下戴个帽子
and have you considered wearing a hat?
看起来会高很多
It can make you look taller.
不必了  琳赛  帽子是你的风格
No, Lindsay, hats are your thing.
噢  谢天谢地
Oh, thank goodness.
幸亏说出这句话的人不必是我
I didn't want to have to be the one to say that.
而且我发现  这不是我的问题  是韦斯的问题
And I realized, it's not my problem. It's Wes's.
如果他因为我矮就不喜欢我
And if he doesn't like me because I'm short,
那他就是个坏蛋
then he's a jerk...
一个有着淡褐色眼睛的梦幻般的坏蛋
A dreamy, hazel-eyed jerk.
我才不会告诉他这个呢
And I'm going to tell him that.
你说的时候
And while you're at it,
顺便提一下他那轮廓分明的下巴和飘逸的头发
mention his chiseled jaw and perfect hair.
他会伤心死的
That'll get him.
你确定不是因为你想多了
Are you sure this isn't just all in your head?
也许他不在意你矮不矮的问题
Maybe he doesn't care that you're short.
那他为什么昨天完全无视掉我呢
Then why else would he have blown me off like that yesterday?
啊  这颗恶心的痘痘就是弄不掉
Ugh. This gross pimple will not go away.
它消失之前  我不想让任何女生看到我
I don't want any girls looking at me until it's gone.
呃  对不起  没空
Uh, sorry, not now.
臭痘痘
Stupid pimple.
嘿  韦斯  我知道你为什么不想看我
Hey, Wes. I know why you won't look at me,
原因很让人恶心
and it's disgusting!
你非常讨人厌  而且你恶心到我了
You are a repulsive person and you make me sick.
只是颗痘痘而已  它会消掉的
It's just a pimple. It'll go away!
等一下  痘痘  什么痘痘  我不知道原来你长了痘痘
Wait! Pimple? What pimple? I didn't know about your pimple!
对不起  我一直在说痘痘
Sorry! I keep saying pimple.
他怎么了
What's up with him?
长痘了
Pimple.
我和他彻底没戏了
I really blew it with him.
我以为每个人都因为我矮
I thought everyone was looking
而用异样的眼光看我
at me differently because of my size but,
可能真的只是我想多了
maybe it really was all in my head.
就像根本没人注意到韦斯的痘痘一样
Just like probably no one even noticed Wes's pimple.
嘿  也许别人一样没有发现你的头发短了
Hey, maybe it's the same with your hair.
我头发怎么了
What about my hair?
我是说  可能别人不觉得你的头发有你想象那么糟
I mean, maybe no one else will think it's as bad as you do.
不是的  真的很难看
Oh, no. It's bad.
但是别人总会看到的
But everyone's going to see it at some point,
所以我不如用这个来做件好事吧
so I might as well use that to do some good.
喂  长痘的
Hey, pimple boy.
嘿  小伙子  不要为我妹妹说的话难过
Hey, man. Don't feel bad about what my sister said.
我们每个人都会有难堪的缺点
We all have our hideous flaws.
起码你看上去不是这样的
At least yours doesn't look like this...
你们全家都这么坏
Your whole family is so mean!
我觉得我们都学到了些东西
Well, I think we all learned something here.
我头发的迷人之处不在于长短
The amazingness of my hair was never in its length.
是啊  我们就学到了这个
Yes. That's what we learned.
艾芙莉明白了
Avery figured out that just
只因为她自己对一些事难为情
because she was self-conscious about something
并不代表每个人都是这样看的
didn't mean that everyone else was looking at it the same way.
而我也悟出了一个道理
And I figured something out, too,
多亏泰勒帮了我一个小忙
thanks to a little help from Tyler.
给你  斯坦
Here, Stan.
你想我们的时候  就和它们玩吧
Whenever you miss us, you just play with these.
谢谢  泰勒
Thanks, Tyler.
对了  还有个好消息
Oh, and the good news is
它们不是芝士做的  所以你不会吃掉它们
they're not made of cheese, so you won't eat them.
永远不要断定一条狗一定不会吃掉什么东西
Never assume a dog won't eat something.
真不敢相信我吃了个弹簧
I can't believe I ate a spring.
我希望我拉出来时
When I poop that out,
它不会蹦回我屁眼里
I hope it doesn't bounce back in.
猜猜同学们今天给我的午餐取了个什么名字
Guess what they called my lunch today?
叫鲁本三明治
A Reuben sandwich.
是以一个叫鲁本的孩子命名的
Named after a really smelly kid named Reuben,
他又难闻又喜欢把他内裤穿在裤子外面
who wears his underwear on the outside of his pants.
克洛伊  我真的很用心地给你做了顿很美味的午餐
Chloe, I really upped my game and made you an amazing lunch.
如果你能吃掉这个  我就不埋怨你
If you can eat this, I'll stop complaining.
班尼特  过来这里
Bennett, come here.
让我们告诉克洛伊这个三明治有多好吃
Let's show Chloe what a great sandwich this is.
我
Me?
你吃一半  我吃一半  支持我一下
You eat half, I'll eat half. Support me on this.
呃  我也想支持你
Well, I want to support you,
但我刚好有异常强烈的反胃现象
but I have an abnormally strong gag reflex.
- 你也太假了吧  - 我不想吐出来
- You're being dramatic... - I don't want to throw up...
- 吃了它  - 好吧
- Eat it! - Okay!
吃就吃
Okay.
我能咽下去的
I can do this.
别这样  不是很
Come on, it is not so...
继续啊  难吃的还在后头
Keep going. It gets worse.
这是软骨
That's cartilage.
吃完了
There.
- 好吃  - 唔  真好吃
- Good. - Mm mm. Good.
现在吃土豆沙拉
Now the potato salad.
明天我给你十块钱买午餐
Tomorrow I'll put ten dollars in your lunch.
我别无他求
That's all I'm asking.
噢  难道是弹簧  我特别害怕
Oh, not the spring! I was afraid of that.